Roujing, are you okay?
I'm fine.
He just passed out.
Good thing no one got killed.
If I hadn't dared to come,
you would have killed someone.
With all this noise,
why didn't anyone stop him?
You know my husband's temper.
Stopping him is provoking him.
No one dares to.
Zhangxin,
you're the only one in this house
who dares to treat me well.
Thank you.
You need to leave now.
Otherwise, when he wakes up,
he won't let you off.
-I'm not leaving.
-Go, now!
With He Shizai's power in Rongcheng,
I can't escape no matter where I go.
Then I'll take you to Madam He
and ask her to help you.
Can you contact Master He?
Dad never lets anyone disturb him
when he goes abroad.
He only contacts Madam He.
Looks like I can only wait
until Dad comes home.
Let's go. We'll go find Madam He.
Madam He.
This isn't the first or second time
the eldest young master
has domestically abused his wife.
If this continues...
It's bound to cause trouble
sooner or later.
You called me here this late
to tell me what to do?
Madam He,
Zhangxin is just looking out for me.
Please don't blame her.
The He family holds
a pivotal position in Rongcheng.
Over the years,
Master He has helped the poor and needy.
He's not just an entrepreneur,
but a beloved philanthropist.
The He family has always
valued its reputation.
Are you going to let everything
Master He worked so hard for
be ruined overnight?
Come here.
I know it's not easy for Mrs. He
to manage the estate alone.
But since you're Master He's better half,
you should share his burden,
shouldn't you?
Mrs. He,
I'm sorry.
We disturbed your sleep.
We'll leave right now.
Let's go.
To think the eldest young master
of the He family
was beaten by a servant.
Does it hurt?
Li Zhangxin really hits hard.
I'd say it was a well-deserved beating.
Ah!
Do you think the Master doesn't know
about the domestic violence?
He's just turning
a blind eye for now.
Once it's exposed,
will he let you off?
It's all that bitch's fault.
Just looking at her makes me mad.
He Shi,
stop causing trouble for me.
Don't be angry.
Let me help you
cool down.
In this house,
I will always be Mrs. He.
I'm warning you.
No more domestic violence.
If you must hit me,
do it somewhere private.
I'm sorry, Zhangxin.
It's all my fault
that you offended He Shi
and Mrs. He.
It's fine.
I think Mrs. He
has taken it to heart.
Haven't you ever thought about a divorce?
Before we got married,
He Shi made me sign
a strict prenup.
If we divorce,
I leave with nothing.
Then
I wouldn't even be able to keep
my baby.
Don't go back tonight.
If He Shi wakes up,
he'll definitely keep coming after you.
If you don't mind,
you can stay here.
The family motto echoes
with a lasting charm,
the earnest words in the hall linger on.
The love between parents
and children is like a net,
the respect among brothers
is like flying geese.
Let me admire my beautiful self.
Not bad.
Ah, Li Zhangxin,
it was you.
You're awake.
Did I see it wrong?
Li Zhangxin!
The butler said
a batch of frozen goods arrived
and asked you to check them.
Open the door!
Is anyone there?
Open the door! Is anyone there?
Is anyone there? Open the door!
Open the door!
Open up!
Is anyone there?